Zeyad El-Salhy

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

SHARQIA, EGYPT SD 44745

+2 01020730202 # ZIZOBAHAAPERSONAL@GMAIL.COM

Summary

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 2 years of related experience.

Skill Highlights

- Front-end frameworks
- User interface
- Document object model
- Time management

- Responsive design
- API design
- Creativity
- Adaptability

Experience

Full Stack Developer - 08/2021 to now

Freelancer

- Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.
- Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.
- Consulted with engineering team members to determine system loads and develop improvement plans.
- Coordinated with other engineers to evaluate software and hardware interfaces.
- Adjusted design parameters to incorporate new features.
- Developed clear specifications for project plans using customer requirements.
- Discussed project progress with customers, collected feedback on different stages and directly addressed concerns.

Mobile app developer- 02/2022 to now

AdsPro Software, New York

- Consulted regularly with customers on project status, proposals and technical issues.
- Transformed existing software to correct errors, upgrade interfaces, and improve efficiency.
- Cooperate diligently with other IT team members to plan, design, and develop smart solutions.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering 2021-current

Zagazig University, Faculty of Engineering